<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Coachella Valley Real Estate Podcast with Josh Jelmberg</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Jelmberg Team, Inc. - your professional Coachella Valley Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Josh Jelmberg</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2020-11-04 09:19:30 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Josh Jelmberg</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>melissa@jelmberggroup.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Coachella Valley Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Jelmberg Team, Inc. - your professional Coachella Valley Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Can Deliberate Practice Help You Build Your Business?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-deliberate-practice-help-you-build-your-business.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-09-28 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Josh+Jelmberg/Videos/Recruiting/How+Can+Deliberate+Practice+Help+You+Build+Your+Business_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Deliberate practice can destroy the barriers preventing you from continuously improving.

‘Kaizen’ is a concept heard normally when discussing quality in manufacturing. It’s a Japanese word that literally means “continuous improvement.” It’s a persistent desire to do better, to excel beyond the current level of expertise. It’s very much a positive state of mind in that you only look backward on successes or mistakes to celebrate, learn, move forward, and grow. There is no place to either rest on our past successes or dwell on past mistakes.

Maybe the most famous study that included this concept of continuous improvement was done by Anders Ericsson. Ericsson is a cognitive psychologist who spent his career studying how experts acquire world-class skills. He studied Olympic athletes, chess grandmasters, renowned concert pianists, prima ballerinas, PGA golfers, and expert radiologists—he is the expert on experts.



The type of practice that Ericsson found most world-class experts to engage in is what he calls deliberate practice, to which there are four parts:

1. Stretch goal. The focus is on a very specific aspect of performance that is trying to be improved. This is generally one of the weaker aspects of one’s performance.

2. 100% focus, or practice with full effort and concentration. It’s not practicing while listening to a podcast, or posting on social media and having a text conversation with a friend. It’s total focus and effort.

3. Feedback. Feedback is ideally immediate, data-driven, and easily measurable. “Did I make the shot or not.” “What was my time?” “Did I hit the receiver in stride?”

4. Reflect and refine. Feedback is typically negative (e.g., “Here is what you didn’t do that you set out to do”). What world-class experts do that most of us don’t is truly open themselves up and listen to feedback. They reflect, make adjustments, and start the cycle over again.



It’s this process of deliberate practice done over and over and over that allows us to continuously improve, grow, and realize our true potential.

“If we can embrace and fall in love with the process of deliberate practice, the sky’s the limit for what we are trying to accomplish.”

The Seahawks just whooped the Patriots on a recent Sunday night football, and in his post-game press conference, Russell Wilson described how deliberate practice helps his team make plays like the exceptional ones made to win the game. He said, “People talk about 10,000 hours to be great; I feel like I’ve spent 30,000 hours making those types of plays. You spend so much time in the offseason, with just the obsession of doing it over and over and over and over again, working at it, perfecting it. It’s not perfect, let’s do it again, let’s rep it again, let’s get it right. Those guys (his teammates) have completely bought into the process of it all, completely bought into the work ethic of it all.” He goes on to say, “I love winning. I love the process of winning. I love the process of the week (of practice). I love that more than the end result even.”

If we can embrace and fall in love with the process of deliberate practice, the sky’s the limit for what we are trying to accomplish.

So, as far as our team goes, one of the main ways continuous improvement is achieved is with the help of coaching and accountability from our success manager. Agents meet with our success manager once a week and receive feedback on the goals they created themselves and are then coached on their next steps to move forward. Along with this accountability and coaching, we provide two training sessions a week that agents are able to take advantage of. Couple this with the tools and leads we provide and the growth potential for our agents’ skills and business are constrained only by their desire to achieve them.

If you have a passion to be a great Realtor and find yourself plateauing, or just not sure what to do next to perpetuate Kaizen and stay on the path of growth in your career, give me a call to schedule a private one on one meeting. I would love to help you!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Josh+Jelmberg/Videos/Recruiting/How+Can+Deliberate+Practice+Help+You+Build+Your+Business_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Josh+Jelmberg/Videos/Recruiting/How+Can+Deliberate+Practice+Help+You+Build+Your+Business_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Deliberate practice can destroy the barriers preventing you from continuously improving.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Deliberate practice can destroy the barriers preventing you from continuously improving.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How To Overcome The Top Seller Misconceptions In a Seller’s Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-overcome-the-top-seller-misconceptions-in-a-sellers-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-07-22 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Josh+Jelmberg/Videos/Recruiting/Videos/How+To+Overcome+The+Top+Seller+Misconceptions+In+a+Sellers+Market.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here are the most common seller misconceptions we face and how we overcome them.

These past few weeks have been extraordinary. The market in the Coachella Valley is in overdrive as pent-up demand from buyers has been unleashed; many are jumping into the market to take advantage of low interest rates. The Jelmberg Team has put 37 transactions in escrow in the last 43 days alone!

We’ll see in the coming weeks how the governor’s new restrictions affect buyers’ mindsets, but the high demand we have experienced over the last month and a half, along with the valley’s low inventory, puts us in the middle of a pretty strong seller’s market. Today I am going to share the top misconceptions we have faced from sellers in today’s market and how we overcome them.

The term “seller’s market” is not used as often for the desert real estate market as it is for places like Orange County or Seattle. Unless a seller is at the right price point in Palm Springs, La Quinta, Indio, Cat City, DHS or Coachella right now (all markets with less than 3.5 months of sales), getting three above-asking-price offers like you may see in the coastal markets probably isn’t a reality. Being prepared with hyperlocal market data to dispel or confirm these hopes and setting the right expectation for a potential seller are the first orders of business once the price is discussed at a listing presentation. This includes communicating a clear plan for any out-of-pocket expenses to cover repairs or staging that will maximize your clients’ proceeds.

The other common misconceptions a seller can bring to a listing presentation revolve around the value of an agent and our commission in a seller’s market. Now more than ever, we have to make the value we bring to our potential clients very clear. That involves showing them that by partnering with us, they will be able to safely sell their home for the highest price faster and with less hassle.

“Unless a seller is at the right price point in the right community, getting three above-asking-price offers like you may see in the coastal markets probably isn’t a reality.”

One way we do this is to have a personalized and detailed marketing plan. A listing’s exposure to the right buyers is key for a seller to maximize their sales price. Our agents employ the highly effective Jelmberg Advantage—a specific and comprehensive plan leveraging the Jelmberg Team’s 20 years of national marketing experience to drive traffic to our listings via digital, print, and social media strategies. The plan includes 360° virtual tours through Matterport, which provides agents inside and outside our office the opportunity to have their clients preview our listings virtually anywhere in the world. Our listings are also shared with our agents’ best-fit clients from our database of over 20,000.

Another way to show your value is to explain to your potential seller how you will get them from contract to close virtually, safely, and with less hassle. We have an in-house contracts manager, listing coordinator, and marketing department focused solely on their respective expertise who have been through well over 1,000 transactions together. They work with our agents and their clients to get them from the signed purchase or listing agreement to close efficiently, and with a proactive approach that handles potential issues before they become a problem. We can do all of this almost exclusively virtually if needed. This allows a level of service for our clients that is unmatched while saving our agents a minimum of 20 to 40 hours per transaction that they can use to show a property, negotiate, and write deals.

Commission discounting will likely consistently be an issue for you if you aren’t able to show a seller that your value far exceeds “just sticking a sign in the yard and letting the market take care of the rest.”

Reach out if you have any questions or are curious about the myriad of services we provide our agents. We’d love to help you.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Josh+Jelmberg/Videos/Recruiting/Videos/How+To+Overcome+The+Top+Seller+Misconceptions+In+a+Sellers+Market.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Josh+Jelmberg/Videos/Recruiting/Videos/How+To+Overcome+The+Top+Seller+Misconceptions+In+a+Sellers+Market.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are the most common seller misconceptions we face and how we overcome them.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are the most common seller misconceptions we face and how we overcome them.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Interviewing an Agent About Their Experience With Our Team</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/interviewing-an-agent-about-their-experience-with-our-team.html</link>
        
          <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-06-14 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Renee Marrotte&rsquo;s experience in real estate and on our team.

Renee Marrotte has been an agent with the Jelmberg Team for some time now. I recently sat down with her to talk about her career and experience working with our team:

Why did you get into real estate?

I originally had been in college to become a physician’s assistant, but I didn’t quite make it through the rounds to get into the program because it was so impacted at the time I went. 

The real estate market was going well, and my family had their own real estate company for many years. My mother needed help, so I decided to go to work in real estate. I took to it right away.

When you first got into the industry, what was your vision for your business and your life?

I always wanted to work in sales, but if you’ve ever worked in property management, you’d know that it takes a lot of time. Most of my time was occupied, and I couldn’t grow because all my energy was being spent on rentals. I needed to make a break so I could just concentrate on sales.

“I have more confidence in myself and in what I can achieve.”

How did you hear about us?

I had been looking for a position, and I saw one of your advertisements, so I just applied.

Having been with the team for a while, what can you do now that you didn’t feel comfortable doing before?

I have more confidence in myself and what I can achieve. I’ve learned about many things like video calls and communicating better with different personalities.

If you have any questions about what it’s like to work on our team or what you could gain by joining us, don’t hesitate to reach out. We’d love to hear from you.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Renee Marrotte’s experience in real estate and on our team.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Renee Marrotte’s experience in real estate and on our team.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What’s the Message I Should Communicate to Clients?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-the-message-i-should-communicate-to-clients.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-06-03 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Josh+Jelmberg/Recruiting/Videos/Whats+the+Message+I+Should+Communicate+to+Clients_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here&rsquo;s advice on how to pivot back toward more industry-focused messaging.

With the ever-changing landscape of our nation and the COVID-19 stay-at-home orders, the question our agents keep asking is, “What message should I be communicating to my clients right now?”

There was a time (not that long ago) during this pandemic when we focused solely on how to support our clients with their basic needs and safety. In the last month, I think our conversations have gradually moved from ensuring clients had toilet paper and food to valid interest in real estate. Only take your client leads as far as they are emotionally willing to go, but I think for the most part we’re back to presenting ourselves as the market experts we are.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Josh+Jelmberg/Recruiting/Videos/Whats+the+Message+I+Should+Communicate+to+Clients_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Josh+Jelmberg/Recruiting/Videos/Whats+the+Message+I+Should+Communicate+to+Clients_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s advice on how to pivot back toward more industry-focused messaging.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s advice on how to pivot back toward more industry-focused messaging.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Two Ways to Adapt Your Business to the Current Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/two-ways-to-adapt-your-business-to-the-current-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-05-13 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

 

How do you succeed in the current market? Take a look at some excerpts from our a recent training session to find out how we’re doing it.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>How do you succeed in the current market?</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>How do you succeed in the current market?</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>New COVID Forms / Update</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/new-covid-forms-update.html</link>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-08 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>CAR has provided some forms for our buyers and sellers who want to physically see a property or have their property shown. By signing, buyers and sellers acknowledge the potential risk of having a physical showing. The Listing Agreement Addendum gives the seller the option of who they deem acceptable to enter the property at all. See below for the appropriate situations these forms will need to be used and who will need to provide executed copies before a physical showing.

PEAD

Buyers and buyer agents that are adamant about getting in vacant or occupied property, after we have exhausted all our options for showing the property via pre-shot video, live virtual walkthroughs, etc.

Sellers that are adamant about having their property shown after we have exhausted all our options to get the property shown via pre-shot video, live virtual walkthroughs, etc. Also, if a home is in escrow and an inspector/appraiser/contractor will be accessing the property. 

Contract to Close: For inspectors, appraisers, contractors, walkthroughs, etc.

Please make sure you take a few minutes to read through this form and understand the requirements to show property physically. Take note of paragraph four, section E, No. 5, indicating the requirements for PPE (Personal Protective Equipment) all parties are to wear when physically showing a home: shoe coverings, rubber gloves, mask, etc.

Listing Agreement Coronavirus Addendum&nbsp;

Mandatory for all listings.

CAR Guidelines

In addition to these forms, CAR also released Guidelines for Real Estate Best Practices During COVID-19.

These guidelines require that we have read and understood the recommendations from the CDC on how to protect yourself from the Virus.

Local COVID Update

Along the lines of protection, Riverside County also released a new public health recommendation to wear a face-covering in public (covering mouth and nose). Palm Springs recently made this recommendation mandatory. Face masks are difficult to come by, but pretty simple to make at home.

Watch: How to Make Your Own Face Covering

Read: How to make your own face mask with items you already have at home

Now is the time to take all precautions we can to keep ourselves and loved ones safe and healthy. As we discussed last week, cases in Riverside County are expected to spike towards the end of April or beginning of May. Our hope is, as a whole, our county and valley have taken the necessary steps in previous weeks and the coming weeks to significantly reduce the projected cases this model shows.

Lastly, keep in mind, our current ability to show property physically, could change if:

“A city or county in which you do your business activity has an order with a more restrictive standard regarding what qualifies as an essential service, or more restrictions on activities, those guidelines will still govern the activities of a licensee. In other words, if there is a more restrictive local order, it must still be followed. That order may prevent or limit your ability to conduct real estate activity.”

Additionally, the City of LA has taken steps to suspended physical showings.

We will keep you updated if there are any changes to this mandate locally.

Team Needs

Also, there were some needs expressed in our meeting. As we venture out for groceries, let’s make sure we are picking up:


  Toilet paper
  Paper towels
  Flower
  Yeast


Reach out to Melissa, Lorena, or myself if you have purchased some of these items for the group.

Have a great rest of your week and a happy Easter! We have a lot to be thankful for!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We've received new forms regarding buyers and sellers, as well as updates for our team!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We've received new forms regarding buyers and sellers, as well as updates for our team!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Application of COVID-19 Showing / Inspection Advisory & Agreement</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/application-of-covid-19-showing-inspection-advisory-agreement.html</link>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-27 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

All,

Please see the COVID-19 Showing / Inspection Advisory &amp; Agreement. We are using this form as a “last resort” for:

Buyers that are adamant about getting in vacant or occupied property, after we have exhausted all our options for showing the property via pre-shot video, live virtual walkthroughs, etc.

Sellers that are adamant about having their property shown after we have exhausted all our options to get the property shown via pre-shot video, live virtual walkthroughs, etc.

Contract to Close: For inspectors, appraisers, walk throughs etc, after we have exhausted all options to adjust terms, closing and contingency dates, waiving VP’s, drive-by appraisals etc., to accommodate for the governors stay at home order and social distancing.

We need to take KW in house councils recommendations seriously when he explains:

“Please be advised that this isn’t a “free pass” to get back to business as usual. This does not negate the fact that our E &amp; O, nor any other insurance carrier, will cover any claims made against our firm or you related to COVID-19. This simply gives us a uniform way to document that anyone accessing our listings and/or conducting business has been advised of the risks.”

Call myself, Melissa, or Penny with any questions. Hope this reaches you well!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Please see the COVID-19 Showing / Inspection Advisory & Agreement.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Please see the COVID-19 Showing / Inspection Advisory & Agreement.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Stay At Home Order Clarified By CAR</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/stay-at-home-order-clarified-by-car.html</link>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-21 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Hey Team!

What we are experiencing is unprecedented. I am sharing some info regarding the Stay At Home Order and CAR’s clarification on it, indicating we are no longer able to physically show vacant or occupied property.

However, there are still buyers and sellers that have need, and we still have options to help them. Here's a link to CAR's post on the Stay At Home Order.

Also, if any of you are feeling overwhelmed or discouraged, or you have other needs, please give me a call. Stay connected and stay encouraged!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I am sharing some info regarding the Stay At Home Order and CAR's clarification on it.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I am sharing some info regarding the Stay At Home Order and CAR's clarification on it.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Sales Meeting 3/18/20</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/sales-meeting-31820.html</link>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-17 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Good morning Team! I wanted to share some important info with you this morning. Make sure you are attending the 9 a.m. team meeting (link below).

Topic: Sales Meeting 3.18Time: Mar 18, 2020 09:00 AM Pacific Time (US and Canada)

Join Zoom Meeting:https://zoom.us/j/438043640

Meeting ID: 438 043 640

Watch Heath's video here!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Good morning Team! I wanted to share some important info with you this morning.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Good morning Team! I wanted to share some important info with you this morning.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Josh Jelmberg</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Josh Jelmberg</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Jelmberg Team, Inc. - your professional Coachella Valley Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
