<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Coachella Valley Real Estate Podcast with Josh Jelmberg</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Jelmberg Team, Inc. - your professional Coachella Valley Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Josh Jelmberg</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2020-05-11 11:52:19 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Josh Jelmberg</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>melissa@jelmberggroup.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Coachella Valley Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Jelmberg Team, Inc. - your professional Coachella Valley Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>New COVID Forms / Update</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/new-covid-forms-update.html</link>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-08 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>CAR has provided some forms for our buyers and sellers who want to physically see a property or have their property shown. By signing, buyers and sellers acknowledge the potential risk of having a physical showing. The Listing Agreement Addendum gives the seller the option of who they deem acceptable to enter the property at all. See below for the appropriate situations these forms will need to be used and who will need to provide executed copies before a physical showing.

PEAD

Buyers and buyer agents that are adamant about getting in vacant or occupied property, after we have exhausted all our options for showing the property via pre-shot video, live virtual walkthroughs, etc.

Sellers that are adamant about having their property shown after we have exhausted all our options to get the property shown via pre-shot video, live virtual walkthroughs, etc. Also, if a home is in escrow and an inspector/appraiser/contractor will be accessing the property. 

Contract to Close: For inspectors, appraisers, contractors, walkthroughs, etc.

Please make sure you take a few minutes to read through this form and understand the requirements to show property physically. Take note of paragraph four, section E, No. 5, indicating the requirements for PPE (Personal Protective Equipment) all parties are to wear when physically showing a home: shoe coverings, rubber gloves, mask, etc.

Listing Agreement Coronavirus Addendum&nbsp;

Mandatory for all listings.

CAR Guidelines

In addition to these forms, CAR also released Guidelines for Real Estate Best Practices During COVID-19.

These guidelines require that we have read and understood the recommendations from the CDC on how to protect yourself from the Virus.

Local COVID Update

Along the lines of protection, Riverside County also released a new public health recommendation to wear a face-covering in public (covering mouth and nose). Palm Springs recently made this recommendation mandatory. Face masks are difficult to come by, but pretty simple to make at home.

Watch: How to Make Your Own Face Covering

Read: How to make your own face mask with items you already have at home

Now is the time to take all precautions we can to keep ourselves and loved ones safe and healthy. As we discussed last week, cases in Riverside County are expected to spike towards the end of April or beginning of May. Our hope is, as a whole, our county and valley have taken the necessary steps in previous weeks and the coming weeks to significantly reduce the projected cases this model shows.

Lastly, keep in mind, our current ability to show property physically, could change if:

“A city or county in which you do your business activity has an order with a more restrictive standard regarding what qualifies as an essential service, or more restrictions on activities, those guidelines will still govern the activities of a licensee. In other words, if there is a more restrictive local order, it must still be followed. That order may prevent or limit your ability to conduct real estate activity.”

Additionally, the City of LA has taken steps to suspended physical showings.

We will keep you updated if there are any changes to this mandate locally.

Team Needs

Also, there were some needs expressed in our meeting. As we venture out for groceries, let’s make sure we are picking up:


  Toilet paper
  Paper towels
  Flower
  Yeast


Reach out to Melissa, Lorena, or myself if you have purchased some of these items for the group.

Have a great rest of your week and a happy Easter! We have a lot to be thankful for!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We've received new forms regarding buyers and sellers, as well as updates for our team!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We've received new forms regarding buyers and sellers, as well as updates for our team!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Application of COVID-19 Showing / Inspection Advisory & Agreement</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/application-of-covid-19-showing-inspection-advisory-agreement.html</link>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-27 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

All,

Please see the COVID-19 Showing / Inspection Advisory &amp; Agreement. We are using this form as a “last resort” for:

Buyers that are adamant about getting in vacant or occupied property, after we have exhausted all our options for showing the property via pre-shot video, live virtual walkthroughs, etc.

Sellers that are adamant about having their property shown after we have exhausted all our options to get the property shown via pre-shot video, live virtual walkthroughs, etc.

Contract to Close: For inspectors, appraisers, walk throughs etc, after we have exhausted all options to adjust terms, closing and contingency dates, waiving VP’s, drive-by appraisals etc., to accommodate for the governors stay at home order and social distancing.

We need to take KW in house councils recommendations seriously when he explains:

“Please be advised that this isn’t a “free pass” to get back to business as usual. This does not negate the fact that our E &amp; O, nor any other insurance carrier, will cover any claims made against our firm or you related to COVID-19. This simply gives us a uniform way to document that anyone accessing our listings and/or conducting business has been advised of the risks.”

Call myself, Melissa, or Penny with any questions. Hope this reaches you well!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Please see the COVID-19 Showing / Inspection Advisory & Agreement.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Please see the COVID-19 Showing / Inspection Advisory & Agreement.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Stay At Home Order Clarified By CAR</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/stay-at-home-order-clarified-by-car.html</link>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-21 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Hey Team!

What we are experiencing is unprecedented. I am sharing some info regarding the Stay At Home Order and CAR’s clarification on it, indicating we are no longer able to physically show vacant or occupied property.

However, there are still buyers and sellers that have need, and we still have options to help them. Here's a link to CAR's post on the Stay At Home Order.

Also, if any of you are feeling overwhelmed or discouraged, or you have other needs, please give me a call. Stay connected and stay encouraged!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I am sharing some info regarding the Stay At Home Order and CAR's clarification on it.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I am sharing some info regarding the Stay At Home Order and CAR's clarification on it.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Sales Meeting 3/18/20</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/sales-meeting-31820.html</link>
        
        <author>Josh Jelmberg</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-17 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Good morning Team! I wanted to share some important info with you this morning. Make sure you are attending the 9 a.m. team meeting (link below).

Topic: Sales Meeting 3.18Time: Mar 18, 2020 09:00 AM Pacific Time (US and Canada)

Join Zoom Meeting:https://zoom.us/j/438043640

Meeting ID: 438 043 640

Watch Heath's video here!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Good morning Team! I wanted to share some important info with you this morning.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Jelmberg</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Good morning Team! I wanted to share some important info with you this morning.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Coachella Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Josh Jelmberg</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Josh Jelmberg</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Jelmberg Team, Inc. - your professional Coachella Valley Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
